ADENIRAN OLUWASEUN MICHAEL

Maitama, Abuja | adeniranoluwaseunelvis@gmail.com | 08147405277 |09023887108

PROFILE

An individual willing to learn and adapt to new environments; contributing strong background in solution implementation, excellent services, hard work and team spirit with resultant effect of exceptional success in the organization. Also, to share and apply my knowledge, experience in improving and assisting the continuous growth of an organization, particularly in the field of Political Science, Management, Administration and I.T.

WORK HISTORY

Nigerian Investment Promotion Commission (NIPC), Maitama, Abuja 2020 - 2021 Post Held: NYSC (Administrative Assistance) Department of Strategic Communications **Job Responsibilities:**

- Assistant Secretary
- Processing of data and information, report writing and appraisals
- Secretary to the new Department, Department of Strategic Services August 2021 - Present

Post Held: Media Assistant, Press and Protocol Unit **Job Responsibilities:**

2020 - 2021

- Website Administrator on WordPress (Posting Daily News and Blogs)
- Design and Publishing the NIPC Intelligence, a daily e-newsletter.
- Content Sourcing
- Assisted in planning the Commission's events.
- Handling and assisting in organizing and executing/anchoring interviews both live and on zoom

Nielson Company, Ikeja, Lagos

2015 - 2016 Data

Post Held: Gathering Officer

Job Responsibilities:

- Collection, processing and analysis of data in Lagos.
- General Office administration

Mobile Oil Nigeria Plc, Abule-Egba, Lagos **Post Held: Sales Representative**

2012 - 2013

Job Responsibilities:

- Supervision of the Unit and Department of Staff.
- Assisted in the administrative duties of the department.
- · Sales of Petroleum Products.

EDUCATION

Federal University Lafia, Nasarawa State	2019
Political Science (B.sc) Second Class	
Ewoma College, Lagos State	2012
 National Examination Council (Secondary Certificate Examination) 	
Success Private School, Ogun State	2006

First School Leaving Certificate (F.S.L.C.)

CERTIFICATION/TRAINING

 Attended Practical training for OSIP content managers (NIPC, REA & FMP) for One Stop Investment Platform (OSIP), Nigerian Energy Support Programme ii (nesp ii) conducted by GIZ-NESP 2021

•	Jobberman Soft Skills Training Certification	2021
•	Udemy Full-stack Web Development Certificate (In-view)	2022
•	Aplearn Frontend Web Development Certification Course	2022

SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Expert in Programming languages (Html5, Css3, Bootstrap)
- Intermediate skills in JavaScript, Chrome developer tools, React.js.
- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, Power Point)
- · Content Management and Front-end development on WordPress
- Content Management & Email marketing Design on Mailchimp
- Social Media Management
- Excellent Organizational Skills

OTHER SKILLS

- · Strong interpersonal and communication skills
- Ability to work both individually and as a team player
- Fast-learning ability
- · Good problem-solving skills
- · Self-motivated and goal-oriented
- · Creative writing ability
- · Highly motivated by challenging situations
- · Capacity to work in any environment and under pressure
- Interest: Education, Information and Communication Technology, Media and Press.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

- Human Resource Management Professional (HRM)
 Provider: Dexter & Heros Consulting Ltd, Abuja Date:
 2021
- Project Management Professional (PMP)
 Provider: Dexter & Heros Consulting Ltd, Abuja Date:
 2021
- Customer Service Management Professional (CSM)

Provider: Dexter & Heros Consulting Ltd, Abuja Date: 2021

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Servicom- NYSC, Community Development Service November 2020 - 2021

Position: Secretary

- Volunteer services for 11 months
- Sensitization and education of students on civil rights and duties in F.C.T metropolis
- Kept records of and for the CDS for a year
- Writing official letter and receiving correspondence for the CDS

REFEREES

Available on request